ILGWU. Gus Tyler papers, 5780/096
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Correspondence. Center for International Leadership Seminars [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence. Center for International Leadership Seminars [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence. Economic Policy Council, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Organized Crime [folder 1 of 5], 1973 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Organized Crime [folder 2 of 5], 1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Organized Crime [folder 3 of 5] (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Organized Crime [folder 4 of 5], 1975 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Organized Crime [folder 5 of 5], 1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation Grant Distribution of Income, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Legal Assistance Program, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Meeting, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. "Organized Crime in America" Proposal, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Script on "Human Rights, Fairness and Justice" [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence. The Ford Foundation. Script on "Human Rights, Fairness and Justice" [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Hispanic Policy Development Project [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Hispanic Policy Development Project [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Homework Meetings [folder 1 of 4], 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Homework Meetings [folder 2 of 4], 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Homework Meetings [folder 3 of 4], 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Homework Meetings [folder 4 of 4], 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Institute for the Future [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Institute for the Future [folder 2 of 2], 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The International Society for Panetics, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Area Community [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Area Community [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mid-Continent Regional Educational Laboratory, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Sciences [folder 1 of 4], 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Academy of Sciences [folder 2 of 4], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Sciences [folder 3 of 4], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Academy of Sciences [folder 4 of 4], 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. American Issues Forum [folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. American Issues Forum [folder 2 of 3], 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. American Issues Forum [folder 3 of 3], 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. General, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - National Institute of Education. Vocational Education Study [folder 1 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - National Institute of Education. Vocational Education Study [folder 2 of 5], 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - National Institute of Education. Vocational Education Study [folder 3 of 5], 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - National Institute of Education. Vocational Education Study [folder 4 of 5], 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - National Institute of Education. Vocational Education Study [folder 5 of 5], 1980 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 1 of 8], 1980- 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 2 of 8], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 3 of 8], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 4 of 8], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 5 of 8], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 6 of 8], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 7 of 8], 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - National Research Council. Committee on Occupational Classification and Analysis [folder 8 of 8], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Public Education Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Public Education Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - A. Philip Randolph High School at City College, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Toronto. ILGWU History [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Toronto. ILGWU History [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The United States Conference on Protocol, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - United States Congressional House of Representatives, 1973-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - United States Congress. House of Representatives- Subcommittee on Communications, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - United States Congress. House of Representatives. Subcommittee on International Economic Policy (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - United States Congress. House of Representatives. Subcommittee on Education, Arts and Humanities, 1978- 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - United States Congress. House of Representatives. Testimony by Others, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - United States Congress. Testimony before Subcommittee No. 5 of the House Judiciary Committee, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - United States Congress. Subcommittee on Constitutional Amendments of the Judiciary Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - United States Congress. Subcommittee on Constitutional Amendments of the Judiciary Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - United States Department of Justice [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - United States Department of Justice [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - United States Department of Labor. Diamond Jubilee Symposium [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - United States Department of Labor. Diamond Jubilee Symposium [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - United States Office of Technology Assessment [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - United States Office of Technology Assessment [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - West Virginia Education Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - West Virginia Education Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 1 of 6], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 2 of 6], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 3 of 6], 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 4 of 6], 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 5 of 6], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Women in the Military Service for America [folder 6 of 6], 1988 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 1 of 9], 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 2 of 9], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 3 of 9] (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 4 of 9], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 5 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 6 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 7 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 8 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Workmen's Circle [folder 9 of 9], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Workmen's Circle. "Horizon" Newsletter [folder 1 of 3], 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Workmen's Circle. "Horizon" Newsletter [folder 2 of 3], 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Workmen's Circle. "Horizon" Newsletter [folder 3 of 3], 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - World Veterans Federation. Constitution and Rules, 1963-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - World Veteran's Federation. Lists of Members, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - World Veterans Federation. General [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - World Veterans Federation. General [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - World Veterans Federation. Reception Invitation [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - World Veterans Federation. Reception Invitation [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - World Veterans Foundation. Rotterdam, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Series II. Articles
  - The Agony of New York City's Economy, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Alchemy of the Counter-Revolution, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - American Labor in Politics, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - American Labor Prepares for Solidarity Four, 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Tyler, Gus. "America's Great Export: Jobs" (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 1 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 2 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 3 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 4 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 5 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 6 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 7 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 8 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - "America's Underground Economy" [folder 9 of 9], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "The Anatomy of the Informal Economy" [folder 1 of 2] (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - "The Anatomy of the Informal Economy" [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Foreign Policy and Multinational Labor?" No.12, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - "Another Veteran's Voice on Flag-Burning" (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "The Anti-Chinese Crusade" (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Assignment '68 Pamphlets, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Ave et Vale, Columbus, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Basque-Jewish Connection, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - "Beware of Praise", 1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - "Birthplace of Civilization", 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - "Breaking Party Lines", 1970 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "Building Tomorrow's Labor Leadership", 1957 (Box 15)
  - "Can Anyone Run a City?", 1969 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "Can Our Cities Escape the Threat of Urban Chaos?", 1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Career Education [folder 1 of 4], 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Career Education [folder 2 of 4], 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Career Education [folder 3 of 4], 1972 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Career Education [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "The Case for Hubert Humphrey" (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Community Services in a Changing Community", 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Challenges to American Industries", 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "Changing Face of Labor", 1967 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "City Election at Midpassage", 1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Close Up Foundation, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Clothing Industry is a Bit Threadbare", 1971 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "The Coming Depression", 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 1 of 14], 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 2 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 3 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 4 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 5 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 6 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 7 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 8 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 9 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 10 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 11 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 12 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 13 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Confronting Chaos: America's Role in New World Disorder" [folder 14 of 14] (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Confronting Scarcity", 1974 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - "Congress and the Succession", 1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "The Negro and American Labor Movement", 1968 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "Countervailing Powers Revisited" (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - "Creators and Disturbers" (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "The Crime Corporation" [folder 1 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "The Crime Corporation" [folder 2 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - "The Crime Factor" (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - "Criminal and the Community", 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - "David Dubinsky: A Glimpse of Greatness", 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "David Dubinsky: A Life with Social Significance", 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "The Day it Happened", 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - "The Defects in the Electoral College", 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - "Dependent America" (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "Disfranchise the Old" (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - "Do-Nothing Legislature", 1964 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Don't You Believe the Deficit Isn't A Problem?", 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - "Duel in the ADA" (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - "Economic Factors in Group Life", 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "Economic Issues", 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - "Education in the New Millennium" (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Education in a Democracy" [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Education in a Democracy" [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "Education: The Search for Relevance" (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "Education: Who Needs It?" (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - "Eight Million Pieces of the Action", 1969 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "The Electoral College", 1969 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "Everybody's Core Curriculum", 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - "The Faculty Joins the Proletariat" [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "The Faculty Joins the Proletariat" [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - "Failure of a Dream?", 1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Farmers, Government and Market Economies", 1991 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    English and Arabic
  - "For a Real Supply-Side Economy", 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - "Fresh Breezes in the Labor Movement", 1967 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - "From Priesthood to Proletariat", 1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - "Full Employment", 1977 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "The Future of American Labor" (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter" [folder 1 of 5], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - "George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter" [folder 2 of 5], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - "George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter" [folder 3 of 5], 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - "George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter" [folder 4 of 5], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - "George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter" [folder 5 of 5], 1979 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - "Government and the Democratic Process" (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - "Hail and Farewell Columbus", 1989 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 1 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 2 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 3 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 4 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 5 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 6 of 22], 1980 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 7 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 8 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 9 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 10 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 11 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 12 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 13 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 14 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 15 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 16 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 17 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 18 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 18 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 19 of 21], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 20 of 21], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "The History of Labor in American Politics" [folder 22 of 22], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - "Human Rights, Fairness and Justice", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "Conference on Humanities and Labor", 1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "Increasing Employment Opportunities for Youth", 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "Inside Job: The Looting of America's Savings and Loans", 1989 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "The Intergenerational Struggle", 1970 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - "The Jewish Labor Movement: A Living Legacy" (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "Labor and National Economic Policy" (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Labor in the Metropolis", 1972 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - "Labor in the 1980s: A New Challenge", 1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - "Labor Movement in the United States", 1967 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - "Labor Relations: Will We Survive the 1990s?" (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - "Labor Today", 1972 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - "Laboring to Counterbalance Concentrated Capital", 1991 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - "Labor's Multinational Pains", 1973 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - "Labor's New Era", 1966 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - "Labor's New Horizon", 1966 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "Labor's Transitional Generation: 1955-1980" (Box 18)
  - "Labor's View of Education", 1986 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - League of Women Voters Education Fund Speech, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - "The Legacy of the Jewish Labor Movement", 1965 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Campaign (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - "A Liberal's Case for Humphrey", 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "The Limits of Corporate Responsibility", 1971 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Look for the Union Label: A History of the ILGWU" [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "Look for the Union Label: A History of the ILGWU" [folder 2 of 2], 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Louis D. Brandeis' Way to Jewish Identification", 1966 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Many Imports Far From a Bargain", 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Mexican-Americans Tomorrow [folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Mexican-Americans Tomorrow [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "The Midas Touch", 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Middle American's Share of Pie Remains in the Sky", 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Minimum Wage- Still Fighting the War on Poverty", 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "The Modern Maladies of Misdistribution", 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "The Modes of Labor Education", 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "Money in Politics", 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Newsday. "Multinational", 1973 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Free Trade Union News. "Multinational Corporations: A Global Menace", 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Drafts of "Trade and Multi-Nationals" (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - American Federationist. "Multinationals: A Global Menace", 1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "The Myth of Free Trade" [folder 1 of 5], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "The Myth of Free Trade" [folder 2 of 5], 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "The Myth of Free Trade" [folder 3 of 5], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "The Myth of Free Trade" [folder 4 of 5], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - "The Myth of Free Trade" [folder 5 of 5], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - "The Nation-State versus the Global Economy", 1993 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "New Deal versus Old Deal" (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "New Directions", 1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - "The New Labor Movement" (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - "A New Philosophy for Labor", 1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - "New York: The Fashion City" (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "The 1973 Elections" (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - "Centennial of the Birth of Norman Thomas", 1984 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 1 of 6], 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 2 of 6], 1976 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 3 of 6], 1966 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 4 of 6], 1973 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 5 of 6], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Organized Crime in America [folder 6 of 6], 1971 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "Origins of American Trade Unions" [folder 1 of 3], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - "Origins of American Trade Unions" [folder 2 of 3], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - "Origins of American Trade Unions" [folder 3 of 3], 1988 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - "Our Economy is a Leaky Bucket" Democratic National Platform Committee Speech, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - "Our House Divided", 1988 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - "Out of the Sweatshop", 1984 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - A Path for America: Proposals from the Democratic Left [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - A Path for America: Proposals from the Democratic Left [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - "The Pattern of Garments" (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Politeia: The Quarterly of the American Association of Political Consultants, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - "The Politics of Pat Moynihan- II", 1973 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - "President Dumping", 1967 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - "The Reagan Legacy" (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - "Reapportionment 1972: The Salami Slicing (I)" (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Reflections on Governance", 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "The Return of the Sweatshop" (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "The Return to Elitist Education", 1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "The Riddle of John Roche", 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Riots", 1967 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "The Rise and Fall of the Mafia", 1988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "A Scenario for Fast-Forward" (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Seneca: A Philosopher's Dilemma" (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Seventh Avenue is Still the Garment Center", 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Shoes, Textiles and Specialty Shoes", 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Comment on "Failure of a Dream? Essays in the History of American Socialism", 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Socrates Explains Gorbachev" (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "Solidaridad Siempre" (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Center for Migration Studies Speech (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council Speech, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Platform Committee Speech, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Statement on Loss of Jobs, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - "Taking Keynes Global" (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Technology Transfer: A Labor View, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 21)